To stop the Marxist prosecutors who released rapists and murderers while persecuting Republicans,
conservatives, people of faith, and me, by the way, I will direct a completely overtauld
DOJ to investigate every radical DA and AG in America for their illegal, racist in reverse
enforcement of the law.
And we will bring back a thing called stop and frisk in our cities.
On day one, I will sign a new executive order to cut federal funding for any school pushing
critical race theory, transgender, insanity, and other inappropriate racial, sexual, or
political content on our children, our beautiful children.
Our beautiful children are being destroyed by these maniacs.
I will keep men out of women's sports, it's very easy to do.
And I will sign a law prohibiting child sexual mutilation in all 50 states.
Can you imagine?